Guide to the Alfonte collection of theater programs M1925
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Alfonte collection of theater programs
1945-2002
M1925
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
1.0 Linear feet 2 manuscript boxes
Theater programs collected by Lt. Col. James Alfonte, including Playbill, National Theatre, and others.
Scope and Contents
Theater programs collected by Lt. Col. James Alfonte, including Playbill, National Theatre, and others. Many are from New York City.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Lt. Col. James Alfonte, 2012, and transfer from the Music Library, 2012.
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use.
Alfonte, James, Lt. Col.; Theater--United States--Periodicals.
- Playbill
  - Hostile Witness (Volume 3 January 1966 Number 1) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Annie get your gun (Volume 3 August 1966 Number 8) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Hello, Dolly (Volume 3 August 1970 Issue 5) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Company (Volume 8 February 1971 Issue 2) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Harkness Theatre (December 1975) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Amadeus (January 1982) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Coastal Disturbances (November 1987 Volume 87 Number 11) (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Les Miserables (November 1987 Volume 87 Number 11) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln Center Theater at the Vivian Beaumont (February 1988 Volume 88 Number 2) (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Majestic Theatre (May 1988 Volume 88 Number 5) (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Tennessee Williams' Orpheus Descending (September 1989 Volume 89 Number 9) (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - City of Angels (March 1990 Volume 89 November 3) (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa (February 1992 Volume 92 Number 2) (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Tennessee Williams' A Streetcar Named Desire (April 1992 Volume 92 Number 4) (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Guys and Dolls (December 1992 Volume 92 Number 12) (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Cyrano (November 1993 Volume 93 Number 11) (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Love! Valourr! Compassion! (April 1995 Volume 95 Number 4) (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - 10086 Sunset (April 1995 Volume 95 Number 4) (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - H2$ (April 1995 Volume 95 Number 4) (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Party (July 1995 Volume 95 Number 7) (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Love! Valour! Compassion! (July 1995 Volume 95 Number 7) (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Indiscretions (July 1995 Volume 95 Number 7) (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Victor Victoria (January 1996 Volume 96 Number 1) (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Master Class (February 1996 Volume 96 Number 2) (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (April 1996 Volume 96, Number 4) (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - The King and I (October 1996 Volume 96 Number 10) (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - Present Laughter (March 1997 Volume 97 Number 3) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - The Scarlet Pimpernel (November 1998 Volume 98 Number 11) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Art (April 1998 Volume 98 Number 4) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Parade (January 1999 Volume 99 Number 1) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - The Blue Room (January 1999 Volume 99 Number 1) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - The Price (November 1999 Volume 99 Number 11) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - Ragtime (October 2000 Volume 00 Number 10) (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - Oklahoma! (April 2002 Volume 118 Number 4) (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - The Elephant Man (April 2002 Volume 118 Number 4) (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Hairspray (October 2002 Volume 118 Number 10) (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Frankie and Johnny in the clair de Lune (November 2002 Volume 118 Number 11) (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Nine (March 2003 Volume 119 Number 3) (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Urban Cowboy (March 2003 Volume 119 Number 3) (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Gore Vidal's The Best Man (October 31, 2000 Volume 19, Number 1) (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - The Full Monty (October 31, 2000 Volume 19 Number 1) (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - The Producers (April 2001 Volume 117 Number 4) (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Proof (October 2001 Volume 117 Number 10) (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Thou Shalt Not (October 2001 Volume 117 Number 10) (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Picnic (June 1953) (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - By The Beautiful Sea (July 1954) (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - The Saint of Bleeker Street (March 1955) (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Can-Can (July 1953) (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Kismet (July 1954) (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Wonderful Town (June 1953) (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - bound copies of The Playbill [unfoldered], 1945-1950 (Box 2, Volume 6)
- National (The National Theatre)
  - Kind Sir (October 1953) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Saint Joan (September 1954) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Li'l Abner (September 1956) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Auntie Mame (March 1958) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Miss Isobel (December 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Separate Tables (October 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Time Remembered (October 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - The Teahouse of the August Moon (May 1956) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - Auntie Mame (October 1956) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 9)
  - Ziegfeld Follies (February 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 10)
  - The Vamp (October 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 11)
  - Portrait of a Lady (November 1954) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 12)
  - Tea and Sympathy (November 1954) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 13)
  - Tonight in Samarkand (February 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 14)
  - Anastasia (October 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 15)
  - The Matchmaker (May 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 16)
  - Dear Charles (February 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 17)
  - The Dark is Light Enough (January 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 18)
  - The Skin of our Teeth (July 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 19)
  - Richard II (January 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 20)
  - The Lark (December 1956) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 21)
  - Janus (November 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 22)
  - The Great Sebastians (November 1955) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 23)
  - Hotel Paradiso (March 1957) (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 24)
- miscellaneous programs (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes programs from productions in Washington D.C. and the North Carolina School of the Arts.